嗯。
In was was Nice to meet you.
二零二零年陕西省初中学业水平考试英语听力部分。二零二零年陕西省初中学业水平考试英语听力部分。第一大题：听对话选答案。第一节，听下面十段对话，每段对话后有一个问题，读两遍。请根据每段对话的内容和后面的问题，从所给的三个选项中选出最恰当的一项。
Nice to meet you too.
Question, What are the two speakers doing?
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Question, What are the two speakers doing?
Question, What are the doing?
May I use your ruler please?
Sure, here you are.
Question, What does the girl want to borrow?
No.3 What's wrong with you?
I have a pain in my stomach.
Question, What's the matter with the boy?
Question, What does the girl want to borrow?
Question, What language can Eric speak?
Can Eric speak Japanese?
No, he can't.
He speaks English.
Question, What language can Eric speak?
No.5 Dad, look at the giraffe.
How tall it is.
Can I feed it?
Oh no, we can't.
We can go to the feeding area later.
Question, Where are the two speakers?
Question, I get to the nearest bank?
Pass that building.
It's next to the post office.
It only takes five minutes on foot.
Question, How will the woman get to the bank?
Question, I get to the nearest bank?
Pass that building.
It's next to the post office.
It only takes five minutes on foot.
Question, How will the woman get to the bank?
Question, How can I get Question,
Question, How can I get to the nearest bank?
Question, How can I get
Question, Who has long hair?
Question, What's Question, What's the time, Mike?
Question, time, Question, What's the time, Mike?
第二节，听下面两段对话。每段对话后有几道小题，请根据每段对话的内容和后面的问题。从所给的三个选项中选出最恰当的一项。每段对话读两遍。听第十一段对话，回答第十一、十二。
听第十二段对话，回答第十三至十五小题。
What's the time, What's
Mike? Question, What's the time,
Mike? Question, What's
第二大题：听独白，填信息。本题你将听到一段独白。读两遍，请根据所听内容，用单词或短语完成下列各题。每空限填一个单词。
Question, What's the time,
Question, What's Question, What's the time,
Question, What's the time, Mike?
Question, What's the time,
Mike? Question, Question, the time, Mike?
Question, Mike?
听力部分到此结束。现在。